<Publish>
  <ModId Value="92499" />
  <DisplayName Value="Industries Extended " />
  <ShortDescription Value="A set of boosted manufacturing buildings and QoL" />
  <LongDescription>## Description
This asset pack add specific industrial manufacturing buildings to produce goods in a boosted way having the production multiplier set to 6.
Also there are several Cargo Train Stations to get your trains transport specific kind of resources and goods.
Using CTRL+E by defaults will apply the settings of the Extractor Efficiency that can be configured in the Settings Option of the Menu. I will change this behaivor in future release.
This mod would bring more assets and features to the game related to industries.

## Added Assets
* **Forestry Area Placeholder for Factory**
* **Timber Factory:** Produces only Timber. Need a forestry area deployed to get woods.
* **Furniture Factory:** Produces only Furniture. Need a Timber Factory to get the timber goods as an input.
* **Paper Factory:** Produces only Paper. Need a Timber Factory to get the timber goods as an input.
* **Convenience Food Factory:** Produce only Convenience Food. Need an agriculture area deploy to get livestock.
* **Cargo Train Station Boosted:** A cargo train station that had a lot of storage and quickly loading cargo. It can be upgrade it with additional tracks, specific goods cargo, a park and a parking lot.

## NOTE
This mod is not final version. Still keep working on it and make improvements.

## SPECIAL THANKS
I would like to thanks a lot for the patience on answering my question in order to keep learning on modding CS2 to the people on the Cities Skyline Modding Discord Server.
* krzychu124
* Bruceyboy24804
* StarQ / Qoushik
* TDW
* yenyang
* Tigon Ologdring
... to mention some of them!

## DISCLAIMER
* Safe to remove. This mod will not break your save if removed. However the assets will no longer work.
* This mod may require ***Asset Packs Manager*** which is highly experimental. This mod shouldn't break the save game. But subscribing to assets that require this without the dependency will pop up errors. Worst case you'll get error popups on game load and/or grey boxes in save. But either way, YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE for any damage.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Code/Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot00.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot02.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot03.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot04.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot05.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot06.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot07.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot08.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot09.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Code/Properties/Previews/Screenshot10.jpg" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ForumLink Value="" />
  <ModVersion Value="1.24.0" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.2.0f1" />
  <Dependency Id="78903" />
  <Dependency Id="75426" />
  <!-- I18n EveryWhere -->
  <Dependency Id="79634" />
  <!-- Asset Icon Library -->
  <ChangeLog>## Patch 1.24
* Compiled to be compatible with the new Detailer's Patch #2, game version 1.2.0f1
* Still not final version, working in adding more assets.</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/UkKAfRqfCn" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Javapower77/cs2-industries-extended" />
</Publish>